<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days</string>
    <string name="introduction">I hope you take care of yourself.</string>
    <string name="tip_1">Drink 3 full-glasses of water today. Easy right?</string>
    <string name="tip_2">Go out for a walk. Doesn\'t matter how long or where just get those feet moving. </string>
    <string name="tip_3">Meditate for 10 minutes. Find a quiet place free of distractions. If you are unable, find a 5–10 meditation challenge online to nod along to.</string>
    <string name="tip_4">Go to sleep 30 minutes earlier than you usually do. For example, if you tend to sleep at 2am, then on this day sleep at 1:30am. Sleep is very important</string>
    <string name="tip_5">Have a chat via phone/text with anyone you appreciate and love. It could be with your close friend or family. </string>
    <string name="tip_6">Sit back and relax (or jam out) listening to a song/artist you really like. If you have an album, great. If you have it on your phone, wonderful.</string>
    <string name="tip_7">Today, you will write a 1500 word essay! Just kidding, but it does involve some writing. It won\'t be much I promise. Grab a small piece of paper and something to write with. Write down something that made you laugh or smile recently. It can be from within the past week or even before that. Just write something down.</string>
    <string name="tip_8">Congratulations! It\'s been a week! If you made it this far, then I am proud of you. I think it\'s time for me to listen to you for a change. For today, write down something YOU want to do. Give yourself a challenge and accomplish it. Don\'t make it too easy! If you need ideas, you can always ask for advice from day 5.</string>
    <string name="tip_9">This is probably the most difficult challenge in this list. You are going to ask for help. Maybe you are struggling with procrastination, share that with someone and ask for advice. Find something you have trouble with and seek some form of guidance. Reflect on yourself, no one is perfect and we all could always use help from one another.</string>
    <string name="tip_10">Seeking help can be a daunting task. So today we\'re recuperating! Take a lazy day off. Stay in your PJs, watch a movie (or two), have a snack and enjoy yourself!</string>
    <string name="tip_11">Let\'s do some clean-up today! Unfollow/unsubscribe all negative social media accounts that make you feel bad or that you deem negative. Why follow something that makes you feel down?</string>
    <string name="tip_12">There is a saying, "You are what you eat". So let\'s make something healthy today. Get some vegetables, salad and fruits to make something nice to eat. Even if it\'s a simple sandwich with lettuce and tomato, it counts!</string>
    <string name="tip_13">Donate to your local charity. Remember that box that\'s been collecting dust? Is there toys or clothes you never use? Give something back, donate to others who are in need. You would have helped someone out, it is a good feeling.</string>
    <string name="tip_14">Read a book. Before you ask, it doesn\'t have to be the whole book. Try to get through 20 pages. Take some time for yourself, maybe put on some music and find a nice corner.</string>
    <string name="tip_15">Do whatever you want this day! But that being said, for the night try keep it phone-free. It\'s hard to avoid a blue screens of technology nowadays but will it hurt by going one night without it? Put your phone down and do something else. Exercise? Meditate? Have an early night? Anything but the use of a bright screen!</string>
    <string name="tip_16">Clean your desk/room/house/apartment! How many times have you came home and find yourself in front of a massive mess? Clothes everywhere, bed not made etc. I know I\'m guilty. So, for today, clean up what you can. It not only makes the place look much nicer but it will make you feel much better.</string>
    <string name="tip_17">Give someone a compliment! Someone meaning anybody! Your barista, co-worker, family, friends…anybody! The compliment can be as simple as "I like your shirt today". Give it a try.</string>
    <string name="tip_18">30 minutes of Yoga. Don\'t knock it till you try it. We all know this list was going to have yoga in it someday. If you\'ve never done yoga before find a beginner one on YouTube and follow the workout. Hopefully, you feel much better and maybe even gained a new hobby!</string>
    <string name="tip_19">Write down things you are thankful for. If you are looking for a bigger challenge, tell someone who you are thankful for in person.</string>
    <string name="tip_20">Make-up free day! Or if you don\'t use make-up or any beauty products just have a natural day. Let your hair down and go natural. This challenge is to show you don\'t need to impress anyone.</string>
    <string name="tip_21">Today we are going to adopt a new habit/hobby. Anything you want! Is there something you always wanted to try? Gardening? Knitting? Cooking different meals? Video games? Anything you want! If you find something interesting, give it a shot!</string>
    <string name="tip_22">Easy challenge for you. On a sticky-note, write a quote or motivational speech that means a lot to you. Stick it somewhere you see frequently. Every time you see it, you will be reminded of that quote/speech.</string>
    <string name="tip_23">Do a random act of kindness. An easy but meaningful task for today. Any random act of kindness, for example, opening the door for someone, giving someone some flowers, help someone with grocery, to a chore for someone, give your dog/cat some attention. Just a little random act of kindness. It\'s much better when you don\'t expect anything in return, do it for your own happiness.</string>
    <string name="tip_24">It\'s time for a WORKOUT! It doesn\'t have to be too long. More like a 30 minute session. Do as much as you can, you can even do this at home. If you don\'t know where to start, YouTube has great resources for exercises.</string>
    <string name="tip_25">Treat yourself day! Go for a walk and if you see sweet shop buy yourself a treat! Be kind to yourself. Have an ice-cream, buy that thing you wanted, treat yourself today!</string>
    <string name="tip_26">Give some spare change to the homeless. I don\'t know about you but there is a lot of homeless people where I\'m from. If there isn\'t any in your area, you can donate online. I\'m not asking you to send your life savings. Only if you can, donate enough for a meal or drink. An amount small to you but to them, it\'s everything. If you see someone struggle, you help them out, you don\'t step over them. And this goes out to everyone, if you\'re struggling, get it out of your system, there are people out there who will help you. This can be someone on social media or a professional. We are here to listen to you, we will help you out as much as possible. Do you know why? Because we care. </string>
    <string name="tip_27">Write down everything positive about you. Once again, grab that pen and paper and trot down anything you love about you! So, your smile? Hair? Eyes? Personality? Your clothes? Your taste in films/music? Your kindness? Your ability to never give up? Anything in mind, write it down!</string>
    <string name="tip_28">Go on a solo date. Go out to that place you\'ve never been to. Try new food cuisines you\'ve been interested in but never tried. Watch that movie you wanted to see. Have a good time.</string>
    <string name="tip_29">Brainstorm some bad habits you have. Try not to do it for today!</string>
    <string name="tip_30">The last day! Congratulations, you have made it this far! I hope this list has been keeping you busy. If you\'ve been keeping up then for this final day we will do something for the future. We are going to write a letter for ourselves a year from now. As you\'ve completed this 30 Day Challenge, write down everything you\'ve learnt about yourself and how you\'ve managed to make it this far. This time next year, you\'ll be opening the letter and it will remind you of the person you once were and how much you\'ve changed. Believe you me, when someone is feeling down and unhappy, it\'s incredibly hard to stick to a routine as there seems to be no motivation for anything. By completing this challenge, you\'ve not only shown me, but you\'ve shown yourself how strong and disciplined you are as a person. This time next year, you\'ll open your letter and it will all come back to you. You\'ll be reminded how far you\'ve come and where you once were.</string>
</resources>